<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>/biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/biography/</guid>
      <description>Baoying HUANG Ph.D. candidate, GSMIEEE Macao Institute of Systems Engineering and Collaborative Laboratory for Intelligent Science and Systems Faculty of Innovation Engineering Macau University of Science and Technology (MUST) Baoying Huang received a B.S. degree in Network Engineering and an M.S. degree in Computer Science and Technology both from the School of Computer Science and Technology, Guangdong University of Technology (GDUT), Guangzhou, China in 2016 and 2019, respectively. She is currently pursuing the Ph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/</guid>
      <description>I regard it as a privilege to have had the opportunity to collaborate with supervisors, students, and staff members of exceptional talent: Supervisors Prof. Naiqi Wu (IEEE Fellow, Macau University of Science and Technology, Doctoral Supervisor, 2019-now), Email: nqwu@must.edu.mo Prof. Yan Qiao (IEEE Senior Member, Macau University of Science and Technology, Doctoral Co-Supervisor, 2019-now), Email: yqiao@must.edu.mo Prof. Haibin Zhu (IEEE Senior Member, Nipissing University, Collaborative Doctoral Supervisor, 2016-now), Email: haibinz@nipissingu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services And Awards</title>
      <link>/professional-services-and-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/professional-services-and-awards/</guid>
      <description>Professional Committees To be continued; Editorial Services To be continued; International Conference Services To be continued; Reviewer of International Journals IEEE Transactions on Systems, Man, and Cybernetics: Systems (T-SMC:Systems) IEEE Transactions on Automation Science and Engineering (T-ASE) IEEE Transactions on Computational Social Systems (T-CSS) Reviewer/Program Committee Member of International Conferences To be continued; Awards 1. Recipient of the Outstanding Master&#39;s Graduate of Guangdong Province (Guangdong Province Department of Education, 2019).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Fig. 1. Cluster tools: (a) single-arm robot and (b) dual-arm robot. Fig. 2. Role-based Collaboration (RBC) Research Interests Semiconductor Manufacturing Systems Scheduling and Optimization Role-based Collaboration (RBC) Human-Machine Systems Computational Social Simulation Pre-print B. Huang, N. Wu*, and Y. Qiao, Collaborative Scheduling for Single-arm Cluster Tools with an Equipment Front-End Module Subject to Chamber Cleaning Requirements, IEEE Transactions on Systems, Man, and Cybernetics: Systems (IEEE T-SMC: SYSTEMS), 2023. Q. Jiang, D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description> To be continued; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/image/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
